What did Israel do in Latin America and why we should talk about it?
Well, let's talk about it.
Did you guys know that Israel helped and trained Guatemalan special forces to massacre indigenous people in the killing fields?
This led to 200,000 indigenous Mayans dying at the hands of Israeli trained people.
Do you guys remember when the 43 students in Mexico went missing and it turned out that the government tried carving it up?
Well, did you guys know that Israel helped the Mexican government cover that up by sending espionage and counter-intelligency units?
Did you guys also know that Israel helped General Pinochet come to power in Chile by overthrowing President Allende?
This is actually my favorite one.
Did you guys know that Israel hired ex-Nazi officers from World War II to train and help Bolivian far-right militias execute and kill indigenous people and socialist leaders such as Che Guevara, who was a revolutionary stationed in Bolivia at the time?
Did you guys also know that Israel helped train the far-right militias in the Salvadorian Civil War that massacred and killed the indigenous resistance movement?
This should not come as a surprise.
The United States and Israel terrorizing Latin America?
It's to be expected.
Two settler, colonial, genocidal countries working together to erase indigenous people in Latin America?
We've seen that before.
This time it will not happen again.
We need to organize, take action, and condemn these nations.
We'll be together.
This time it will be over time.
We're out of time.
Let's go.
Cheers!
Hey, Çok 좋은usions!
What's up?
Cheers!